Finding Aid for the Donald Spoto Papers LSC.1563
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Lawrence Olivier, Series 6
  - Interviews by Spoto
    - Alexander H. Cohen and Hildy Parles, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Sir Peter Hall, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Robert Wagner, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - George Roy Hill, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Ronal Pickup and Peter Plouviez, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Felix Barker and Virginia Fairweather, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      2 cassettes (3 parts).
      - Felix Barker Interview, 1989 November 18-25; yrlsc_1563_039_19_1a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Barker, Felix, 1917-1997; Fairweather, Virginia; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:41) (Box 39, Case 19)
        Transcribed from container: "Side A- Felix Barker, interviews at his London home, 18 Nov 89. Side B- Part one of interview with Virginia Fairweather at her Chichester home 25 Nov 89."
      - Virginia Fairweather Interview Part 1, 1989 November 25; yrlsc_1563_039_19_1b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Fairweather, Virginia; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:48:01) (Box 39, Case 19)
      - Virginia Fairweather Interview Parts 2 and 3, 1989 November 25; yrlsc_1563_039_19_2a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Fairweather, Virginia; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:30) (Box 39, Case 19)
        Transcribed from container: "Parts 2 and 3 of 3-part interview with Virginia Fairweather at her home at 8 Russell Street Chichester on 25 November 1989.
      - Virginia Fairweather Interview Parts 2 and 3, 1989 November 25; yrlsc_1563_039_19_2b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Fairweather, Virginia; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:24) (Box 39, Case 19)
    - Mark Amory, Denys Lasdun and Constance Cummings (part 1), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Constance Cummings (conclusion) and Terrance Morgan (part 1), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Alexander Clark and Marcella Markham, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Anthony Quinn, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - John Goodwin, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - William Gaskill and Peggy Ashcroft, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Jonathan Miller, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Michael Caine, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Mary Evans, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Laurence Evans, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      Interview 2
      - Laurence Evans Interview no. 2, 1990 January 11; yrlsc_1563_040_008a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Evans, Laurence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:48:45) (Box 40, Case 8)
        Interview begins at 0:01:14
      - Laurence Evans Interview no. 2, 1990 January 11; yrlc_1563_040_008b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Evans, Laurence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:33:50) (Box 40, Case 8)
    - Diana Boddington, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Terence Young and Laurence Evans (conclusion of last several interviews), 1990 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Terence Young Interview, 1990 January 16; yrlc_1563_040_010a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Young, Terence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:48:00) (Box 40, Case 10)
        Transcribed from container:: "Terence Young interviewed at his London home, 16 Jauary 90. Last 3/4 of side 2 is the last of several interviews with Laurence Evans, conducted 18 January 1990"
      - TY Concl; L. Evans, 1990 January 16-18; yrlc_1563_040_010b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Young, Terence; Evans, Laurence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:39) (Box 40, Case 10)
        Transcribed from container:: "Terence Young interviewed at his London home, 16 Jauary 90. Last 3/4 of side 2 is the last of several interviews with Laurence Evans, conducted 18 January 1990" Interview with Laurence Evans begins at 0:11:30
    - Laurence Evans, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Interview 1[?]
      - Laurence Evans Interview, 1990 January 3; yrlc_1563_040_011a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Evans, Laurence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:44) (Box 40, Case 11)
        Transcribed from container: "Laurence Evans intvw London: 3 January 1990"
      - Laurence Evans Interview, 1990 January 3; yrlc_1563_040_011b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Evans, Laurence; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:44:50) (Box 40, Case 11)
        Transcribed from container: "concl. of Evans, no.1"
    - Douglas Rae and Edward Fox, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Jean Howard Feldman, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Renee Gilmore, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Helen Mirren and Robert Knights, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Denholm Elliott and Euan Lloyd, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Bette Davis (BBC-TV documentary), 1983 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Michael Korda, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Michael Korda Interview, 1990 April 3; yrlc_1563_040_018a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Korda, Michael, 1933-; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:31:47) (Box 40, Case 18)
        Transcribed from container: "Michael Korda, interveiwed at Simon and Schuster 3 April 1990"
      - Michael Korda Interview, 1990 April 3; yrlc_1563_040_018b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Korda, Michael, 1933-; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:31:50) (Box 40, Case 18)
    - Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., 1990 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Stuart Burge and Alvin Rakoff, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Alvin Rakoff (conclusion) and Leslie Evershed-Martin, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Alec McCowen and Maxine Audley, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Pieter Rogers and Rosemary Harris, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Pieter Rogers Interview, 1990 June 20; yrlc_1563_040_023a; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Rogers, Pieter; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:40) (Box 40, Case 23)
        Transcribed from container: "Side A- Pieter Rogers-London-20June 1990. Side B- Rosemanry Harris-London-20 June 1990"
      - Rosemary Harris Interview, 1990 June 20; yrlc_1563_040_023b; Spoto, Donald, 1941-; Harris, Rosemary; 1 Sound Recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:39) (Box 40, Case 23)
  - Spoto's research material
    - Olivier: bibliography. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Olivier: critical articles. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Olivier: miscellaneous. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 1907-1910. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 1910-1916. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 1916-1917. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 1918-1920. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 1921-1924. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1925. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1926. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 1927. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 1928. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 1929. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Birmingham Repertory Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - 1930. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1931. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 1932. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 1933. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 1934. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 1935. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 1936. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 1937. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 1938. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 1939. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 1940. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - 1941. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - 1942. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - 1943. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 1944. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - 1945. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - 1946. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - 1947. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - 1948. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 1950. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 1951. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 1952. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 1953. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 1954. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 1955. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 1956. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - 1957. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - 1958. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 1959. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 1960. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 1961. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 1962. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 1963. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 1964. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 1965. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 1966. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 1967. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 1968. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 1969. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 1970. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 1971. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 1972. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 1973. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 1974. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - 1975. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 1976. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 1977. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 1978. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 1979. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - 1980. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 1981. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 1982. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 1983. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 1984. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 1985. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 1986. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 1987. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 1988. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 1989. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Screenplays, Series 7
  - Spoto, Donald, and John Darretta. Based on an idea by Richard T. Waggoner. Holy terror., 1988 January. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    First draft. Bellwether Productions, Incorporated.
  - Spoto, Donald and John Darretta. Channel crossing: a new age comedy., 1988 July. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    First draft. Original screenplay.